Herbert Halpert collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1: Herbert Halpert's fieldwork
  - Subseries 8: Sound recordings
    - Sub-subseries 6: New Jersey series J, 1937
      - Charles Tilton, AFC 2004/008: SR053; IDB 44236; J28; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Tilton, AFC 2004/008: SR054; IDB 44237; J29; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Tilton, AFC 2004/008: SR055; IDB 44238; J30; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Tilton, AFC 2004/008: SR056; IDB 44239; J31; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Tilton; Charles Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR057; IDB 44240; J32; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Mrs. Lulu Woodenough; Allen Sprague, AFC 2004/008: SR058; IDB 44241; J33; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Allen B. Sprague, AFC 2004/008: SR059; IDB 44242; J34; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Allen Sprague, AFC 2004/008: SR060; IDB 44243; J35; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Joe Malloy, AFC 2004/008: SR061; IDB 44244; J36; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Oliver Minney [?]; Mrs. Sam Hopkins, AFC 2004/008: SR062; IDB 44245; J37; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Oliver Minney [?], AFC 2004/008: SR063; IDB 44246; J38; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Oliver Minney [?], AFC 2004/008: SR064; IDB 44247; J39; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Oliver Minney [?], AFC 2004/008: SR065; IDB 44248; J40; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Mrs. Lily Joy, AFC 2004/008: SR066; IDB 44249; J41; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - William Tester; Mrs. Lila Joy; Tom Test [?], AFC 2004/008: SR067; IDB 44250; J42; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - William Tester, AFC 2004/008: SR068; IDB 44251; J43; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - William Tester, AFC 2004/008: SR069; IDB 44252; J44; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - William Tester, AFC 2004/008: SR070; IDB 44253; J45; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Mrs. Julaney Stevenson; Stella Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR071; IDB 44254; J46; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
        Julaney and Stella are mother and daughter
      - Mrs. Julaney Stevenson; Stella Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR072; IDB 44255; J47; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
        See the note for SR071.
      - Mrs. Julaney Stevenson, AFC 2004/008: SR073; IDB 44256; J48; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Estel; Mrs. Lily Sweet, AFC 2004/008: SR074; IDB 44257; J49; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Marie Sweet; Elvin Sweet; Mrs. Charles Parker, AFC 2004/008: SR075; IDB 44258; J50; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - John Webb, AFC 2004/008: SR076; IDB 44259; J51; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - John Webb, AFC 2004/008: SR077; IDB 44260; J52; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - John Youmans, AFC 2004/008: SR078; IDB 44261; J53; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - John Youmans; Joe White; Howard Applegate, AFC 2004/008: SR079; IDB 44262; J54; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - John Youmans; William Ireland; Joe White, AFC 2004/008: SR080; IDB 44263; J55; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
    - Sub-subseries 7: New Jersey series K, 1938
      All recordings were made in New Jersey, unless otherwise specified. Probably duplicates of originals held by the Archives of Traditional Music, Indiana University
      - Mrs. Charles Parker; Allen Sprague; Charles Parker, AFC 2004/008: SR081; IDB 44264; K1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Mrs. Charles Parker; Charles Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR082; IDB 44265; K2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Mrs. Henry Horn; Mrs. Charles Parker; Charles Parker; George Taylor, AFC 2004/008: SR083; IDB 44266; K3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - George Taylor; Mrs. Mary Parks, AFC 2004/008: SR084; IDB 44267; K4; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Ed Chamberlain, AFC 2004/008: SR085; IDB 44268; K5; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Annie and Ed Chamberlain, AFC 2004/008: SR086; IDB 44269; K6; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Clarence White; Mrs. George White; Ivins Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR087; IDB 44270; K7; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - John Youmans; Frank Johnson; George White, AFC 2004/008: SR088; IDB 44271; K8; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - James E. Edwards (New York); Charles Grant; John Youmans, AFC 2004/008: SR089; IDB 44272; K9/C7; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
        Backed by C7 of NY series
      - Charles Grant; Reuben Edwards (New York), AFC 2004/008: SR090; IDB 44273; K10/C8; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
        Backed by C8 of NY series
      - Newbold Prickett, AFC 2004/008: SR091; IDB 44274; K11; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Ed Chamberlain; Newbold Prickett, AFC 2004/008: SR092; IDB 44275; K12; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Allen Sprague; Mrs. Frank Earlin; Mrs. Mary Parks; Newbold Prickett, AFC 2004/008: SR093; IDB 44276; K13; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Ed Chamberlain; Ivins Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR094; IDB 44277; K14; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Ivins Grant; George White, AFC 2004/008: SR095; IDB 44278; K15; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - George White; William Ireland, AFC 2004/008: SR096; IDB 44279; K16; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Ed Chamberlain; George White, AFC 2004/008: SR097; IDB 44280; K17; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Grant; John Youmans; Annie Chamberlain; Ed Chamberlain, AFC 2004/008: SR098; IDB 44281; K18; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Mrs. Mary Parks; Ed Chamberlain, AFC 2004/008: SR099; IDB 44282; K19; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
    - Sub-subseries 8: New Jersey series L, 1939
      - Ivins Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR100; IDB 44283; L1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Ivins Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR101; IDB 44284; L2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Ivins Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR102; IDB 44285; L3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Ivins Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR103; IDB 44286; L4; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR104; IDB 44287; L5; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR105; IDB 44288; L6; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR106; IDB 44289; L7; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - probably Charles Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR107; IDB 44290; L8; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Freeland C. Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR108; IDB 44291; L9; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
        Halpert has written the first name as "Frelen"
      - Freeland C. Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR109; IDB 44292; L10; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
        See the note for SR108.
      - Freeland C. Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR110; IDB 44293; L11; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Freeland C. Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR111; IDB 44712; L11B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Freeland C. Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR112; IDB 44294; L12; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Freeland C. Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR113; IDB 44295; L13; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Freeland C. Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR114; IDB 44296; L14; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Freeland C. Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR115; IDB 44297; L15; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Freeland C. Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR116; IDB 44298; L16; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Freeland C. Bozarth; Stacy Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR117; IDB 44299; L17; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR118; IDB 44300; L18; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR119; IDB 44301; L19; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Bozarth; Charles Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR120; IDB 44302; L20; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Mrs. Harriet Francis, AFC 2004/008: SR121; IDB 44303; L21; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR122; IDB 44304; L22; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Stacy Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR123; IDB 44305; L23; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Stacy Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR124; IDB 44306; L24; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Stacy Bozarth, AFC 2004/008: SR125; IDB 44307; L25; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
    - Sub-subseries 9: New Jersey series N, 1941
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR126; IDB 44308; N1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Mrs. Lavina Brennan; Ivins McKelvey, AFC 2004/008: SR127; IDB 44309; N2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR128; IDB 44310; N3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
    - Sub-subseries 10: New Jersey, 1941
      A significant number of informants were from New York. The discs were received in a metal canister. Probably duplicates of originals held by the Archives of Traditional Music, Indiana University
      - Charles Hinkley [of Rock Island?]; Jacob Loucks, AFC 2004/008: SR234; IDB 44747; 37; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Jake Loucks (New York), AFC 2004/008: SR235; IDB 44748; 38; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Jake Loucks (New York), AFC 2004/008: SR236; IDB 44749; 39; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Sidney Storms (New York), AFC 2004/008: SR237; IDB 44750; 40; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Sidney Storms (New York), AFC 2004/008: SR238; IDB 44751; 41; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Mrs. Lavina Brennan, AFC 2004/008: SR239; IDB 44752; 42; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Mrs. Lavina Brennan; Ivins McKelvey, AFC 2004/008: SR240; IDB 44753; 43; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Ivins McKelvey, AFC 2004/008: SR241; IDB 44754; 44; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Frank Harker, AFC 2004/008: SR242; IDB 44755; 45; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Frank Harker, AFC 2004/008: SR243; IDB 44756; 46; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - John Wesley Ford, AFC 2004/008: SR244; IDB 44757; 47; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Informats: Doris Tice; John Wesley Ford, AFC 2004/008: SR245; IDB 44758; 48; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
    - Sub-subseries 11: New York series C and D
      - Mrs. Elizabeth Misner, 1938, AFC 2004/008: SR129; IDB 44311; C1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - George Edwards, 1938, AFC 2004/008: SR130; IDB 44312; C2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - George Edwards, 1938, AFC 2004/008: SR131; IDB 44313; C3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - George Edwards, 1938, AFC 2004/008: SR132; IDB 44314; C4; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - George Edwards; Charles Seeley; Frank Edwards, 1938, AFC 2004/008: SR133; IDB 44315; C5; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - George Edwards, 1938, AFC 2004/008: SR134; IDB 44316; C6; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
        For C7 and C8, see K9 and K10
      - George Edwards, 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR135; IDB 44317; D1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
    - Sub-subseries 12: New York City children's games and songs, 1937
      These discs may be dubs of material in the Herbert Halpert New York City collection (AFC 1938/002).
      - New York City children's games, AFC 2004/008: SR017; IDB 44340; 83A/83B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR018; IDB 44704; 47A; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Philadelphia children's games, AFC 2004/008: SR019; IDB 44705; 65A/65B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Philadelphia children's games and songs, AFC 2004/008: SR020; IDB 44706; 66A/67A; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - New York children's games, AFC 2004/008: SR021; IDB 44707; 79B/80A; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - New York children's games, AFC 2004/008: SR022; IDB 44708; 80B/81A; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - New York children's games, AFC 2004/008: SR023; IDB 44709; 81B/82A; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Games from New York State, AFC 2004/008: SR024; IDB 44710; 82B-1; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR025; IDB 44711; 84A; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
    - Sub-subseries 13: New York State recording dubs, 1938
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR136; IDC 57260; Side A: 26A1, 26A2; Side B: 26B1, 26B2, 26B3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR137; IDC 57261; Side A: 27A1, 27A2, 27A4; Side B: 27B1, 28A2, 28A3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR138; IDC 57262; Side A: 28B1; Side B: 28B1, 29B3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR139; IDC 57263; Side A: 29A1, 29A2; Side B: 29B1, 29B2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR140; IDC 57264; Side A: 30A1, 30B1; Side B: 30A2, 30B2, 30B3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR141; IDC 57265; Side A: 30B3, 31A1; Side B: 31A2, 31B1, 33B1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR142; IDC 57266; Side A: 31A2, 31A2, 31A3; Side B: 31B1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR143; IDC 57267; Side A: 32A1, 32A2; Side B: 32B1, 32B2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR144; IDC 57268; Side A: 31B2, 33A2; Side B: 32B2, 32A2, 33A2, 34A2, 34A4, 34A4; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR145; IDC 57269; Side A: 32A1, 33B3; Side B: 32B1, 34A1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR146; IDC 57270; Side A: 34A1, 34A2; Side B: 34B1, 34B2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR147; IDC 57271; Side A: 35A1, 35A2; Side B: 35B1, 35B2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR148; IDC 57272; Side A: 36A1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
        SR142A: first instance of 31 A2 is a false start
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR149; IDC 57273; Side A: 33B2, 35B4, 37B2; Side B: 34A3, 34B1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR150; IDC 57274; Side A: 35A1, 36A2; Side B: 36A1, 36B1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR151; IDC 57275; Side A: 37A1, 37A2, 37B3; Side B: 37B1, 36B2, 37B4; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR152; IDC 57276; Side A: 38A1, 38A2, 38A3; Side B: 38B1, 38B2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR153; IDC 57277; Side A: 39A1, 36B3; Side B: 39A2, 39B1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR154; IDC 57278; Side A: 65B1; Side B: 66A1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR155; IDC 57279; Side A: 66B1, 66B2, 66B3; Side B: 67A1, 67A2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR156; IDC 57280; Side A: 67B1; Side B: 68A1, 68A2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR157; IDC 57281; Side A: 68B1, 68B2; Side B: 69A1, 69A2, 69A3, 69A4; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR158; IDC 57282; Side A: 69B1; Side B: 70A1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR159; IDC 57283; Side A: 70B2, 70B3, 71A1; Side B: 71A1, 71A2, 72A3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR160; IDC 57284; Side A: 71B3, 72A1; Side B: 72A2, 72B1, 74B3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR161; IDC 57285; Side A: 72B2, 73A1; Side B: 73A2, 73B1, 74B4; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR162; IDC 57286; Side A: 73B2, 77A1, 77A2; Side B: 74A2, 74B1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR163; IDC 57287; Side A: 74A1, 75A1; Side B: 75A2, 75B1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR164; IDC 57288; Side A: 75B2, 77A3; Side B: 76A1, 77B1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR165; IDC 57289; Side A: 76B1, 77B3; Side B: 79B2, 80B1, 80B2, 80B3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR166; IDC 57290; Side A: 81A1, 80B3; Side B: 81B1, 81B1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR167; IDC 57291; Side A: 82A1, 82A2; Side B: 82B1, 82B2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR168; IDC 57292; Side A: 83A1, 83A2, 83A3; Side B: 83B1, 83B2, 83B1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR169; IDC 57293; Side A: 84A1, 84B3; Side B: 84B1, 84B2, 84B4, 84B3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR170; IDC 57294; Side A: 85A1, 85A2, 85A3; Side B: 85B1, 84B2, 85B3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR171; IDC 57295; Side A: 86A1, 86A2, 92A2; Side B: 92B2, 92A1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR172; IDC 57296; Side A: 92B3, 93A2, 94A1, 94A2; Side B: 93A3, 94B2, 94B2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR173; IDC 57297; Side A: 94B2, 95A1; Side B: 94B1, 102B3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR174; IDC 57298; Side A: 97B1; Side B: 98A1, 98A2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR175; IDC 57299; Side A: 98A2, 98B1, 98B2; Side B: 99A1, 99A2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR176; IDC 57300; Side A: 99B1, 99B2, 99B3; Side B: 100A1, 100A2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR177; IDC 57301; Side A: 100B1, 100B2; Side B: 101A1, 101A2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR178; IDC 57302; Side A: 101B1; Side B: 102A2, 102A3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR179; IDC 57303; Side A: 102B1, 102B2, 103B2; Side B: 103A1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR180; IDC 57304; Side A: 103B1, 104A2; Side B: 104A1, 104B2, 104B2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR181; IDC 57305; Side A: 104B2, 104B1; Side B: 104B1, 105A1, 105A2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR182; IDC 57306; Side A: 107A1, 107A1; Side B: 105B1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR183; IDC 57307; Side A: 107B1, 107B2; Side B: 110A1, 110A2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR184; IDC 57308; Side A: 110B1, 110B2, 110B3; Side B: 110B3, 111A1, 111A2, 112B1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR185; IDC 57309; Side A: 111A3, 111B1, 114B2; Side B: 111B2, 111B3, 113A1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR186; IDC 57310; Side A: 112B2, 113A2; Side B: 113B1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR187; IDC 57311; Side A: 112A1, 112A1; Side B: 114A1. 114A2, 114A3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR188; IDC 57312; Side A: 114B1, 115B3, 116B2; Side B: 116B2, 116A2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR189; IDC 57313; Side A: 117A1, 117A2; Side B: 117B1, 117B2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR190; IDC 57314; Side A: 118A2; Side B: 118B1, 118B2, 118B3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR191; IDC 57315; Side A: 119A1, 119A2; Side B: 119B1, 119B1, 119B2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR192; IDC 57316; Side A: 120A1; Side B: 120B1, 120B2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR193; IDC 57317; Side A: 121A1, 121A2; Side B: 121B1, 121B2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR194; IDC 57318; Side A: 30A1, 30A1; Side B: 30B1, 30B2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 16 in.
    - Sub-subseries 14: New York State, 1941
      Received in a metal canister. Probably duplicates of originals held by the Archives of Traditional Music, Indiana University
      - Contents: Herbert Halpert singing from Allen Clevenger; New York City children at summer camp, Lake Como, Pennsylvania, AFC 2004/008: SR195_disc1; IDB 44713; 1; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
        SR195_disc1 and disc2 were received in the same sleeve.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR195_disc2; IDB 44824; 1; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
        See the note for SR195_disc1.
      - Contents: New York City children at summer camp, Lake Como, Pennsylvania, AFC 2004/008: SR196; IDB 44714; 2; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Fant Wormuth, AFC 2004/008: SR197; IDB 44715; 3; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Fant Wormuth; Shock Wormuth, AFC 2004/008: SR198; IDB 44716; 4; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Shock Wormuth; Irvan Wormuth, AFC 2004/008: SR199; IDB 44717; 5; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
        Shock and Irvan are father and son
      - Fant Wormuth, AFC 2004/008: SR200; IDB 44718; 6; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Shock Wormuth; Irvan Wormuth, AFC 2004/008: SR201_disc1; IDB 44719; 7; analog, 7A/7B-1; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
        SR201_disc1 and disc2 were received in the same sleeve. See the note for SR199.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR201_disc2; IDB 44720; 7B-2/8A-2; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
        See the note for SR201_disc1
      - Shock Wormuth; Irvan Wormuth, AFC 2004/008: SR202; IDB 44721; 8; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
        See the note for SR199.